Because you're always following her closely,
都是因为你总是紧紧跟着小爱
no one else can approach Aika.
害得其他人都无法接近她
Huh?
咦
It is all because of you
都是因为小佐城你
that Aika now has only
现在班上会跟小爱说话的人
me and you to talk to in class.
就只有我跟小佐城你了
You also look adorable today.
小爱 你今天也好可爱哦
Is it about time we start dating?
差不多可以跟我交往了吧
Not a chance. Go away.
我才不要 你走开
Is it still too early?
看来你还没准备好啊
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我根本不知道你在说什么
Again.
又来了
Poor Natsukawa.
夏川同学也真可怜
But don't you think they go well together?
但你们不觉得他们还满相配的吗
If she really despised him, she wouldn't even bother with him.
如果她真的很反感 应该连理都不会理他吧
Do not worry about it.
算了啦 再怎么说
After all, we are not close enough to interfere in their affairs.
我们也没跟她熟到 可以多管闲事的地步
-Indeed. -Right?
-的确 -对吧
How could this happen?
怎么会这样...
So, if I stop bothering Aika,
所以只要我不再缠着小爱
other people will not think twice?
其他人就不会有所顾虑了吗
What are you up to?
干嘛？
That's right, I'll promote her then.
好 那我就大力宣扬她吧
Huh?
啊？
(Please Enjoy This Spare Chocolate Triangle Pie)
(这是备用的三角巧克力派 请笑纳)
I feel so lonely without Aika around.
跟小爱分开了 人家好寂寞哦
Stop it, Kei.
圭你别闹了啦
Indeed,
的确
I have never seen
我好像还没看过
Natsukawa get close to anyone other than Ashida.
夏川跟芦田以外的人亲近
Now it might be just right.
那现在这种情况说不定正好
What's wrong, Sajo? You've been frowning lately.
怎么啦 佐城 你最近总是板着一张脸
No longer going to find Natsukawa?
你不去找夏川吗
None of your business.
要你管
What about you? Nowhere to go?
那你呢 是没地方去了吗
You! Why bring that up?
你哪壶不开提哪壶啊
It doesn't hurt! Not at all!
不痛 一点都不痛
So, Natsukawa was concerned for me
所以对夏川来说
because she did not want to be left out.
她只是不想落单 才勉为其难地配合我吧
Is daydreaming just a waste of time?
做白日梦也只是在浪费时间吗
I see, so that's your thought, huh?
原来如此 这就是你的想法吗
Huh?
啊？
The person who scared my junior yesterday was you, right?
上次吓到我学妹的人就是你吧
Oh, this is bad. Can you handle that?
糟糕 你没事吧
Don't come over.
别过来
Yes, it was me. I'm truly sorry.
没错就是我 实在是万分抱歉
I was just kidding.
我开玩笑的
Why apologize?
你为什么要道歉
You didn't mean anything bad when you talked to her, did you?
你并非带着恶意跟她搭话的吧
But scaring her is still a fact.
但我的确是吓到她了
Talking to a naive girl in a deserted place
在四下无人之处跟稚气的少女搭话
is a privilege for handsome men in romance manga.
是少女漫画里的帅哥的特权
If I think about it, I should have known I would scare her.
稍微动动脑子也该知道那样会吓到她
Naive…
稚气...
Don't be fooled by her appearance. You should call her senior.
别看她那样 你可得叫她学姐呢
Besides, your actions were commendable.
况且 你的行为本来是值得称赞的
I am relieved to hear you say that.
听学姐这么说 我就放心了
I want to apologize once more.
让我再次向学姐赔不是
Then, I'll take my leave.
那我先告辞了
Hold on a second.
你先等等
What's the matter, Senior Shinomiya?
有什么事吗 四之宫学姐
So, you know me?
原来你知道我是谁？
There are very few students who don't know you.
应该很少人不认识学姐你吧
As an outstanding student council president, you are quite famous.
学姐你可是出众的风纪委员长 有名得很呢
Not at all.
我才没有...
So that's how others see me.
原来其他学生是这样看我的
You appear to be self-critical.
反倒是你 对自己的评价好像很低呢
She treated you that way
当时我学妹之所以会那样对你
because she didn't know how to talk to boys.
是因为她不知道该怎么和男生接触
Even if it wasn't her, I think the result would be the same.
就算不是她 我想结果也还是一样吧
Wait!
你等等
No, this…
不是 这…
I have something to discuss with you.
我有事想跟你商量
Huh?
呃
STUDENT COUNSELING CENTER
(学生指导室)
Now, I am sure you didn't talk to her with any ulterior motives.
现在我可以确信 你跟她搭话并没有心怀不轨了
Because you don't appear to be the type to pretend to be serious.
因为你不像是那种会假正经的人
Is that so? Thank you for the compliment.
是吗 多谢夸奖
So
那个...
the name of the girl you spoke with is Inatomi Yuyu.
你搭话的那个女生叫做稻富由结
She's very diligent and works hard as a student council member.
她是风纪委员 性格认真又非常努力
Oh.
哦
Not just her, all the other student council members too.
不止是她 其他风纪委员也一样
Everyone is proud of their roles.
大家都对风纪委员的工作感到自豪
However,
但是
sometimes they lose confidence and become negative.
他们偶尔会失去自信 变得消极
After all, losing confidence when they see your calm
看到学姐你工作时飒爽的英姿
and composed demeanor at work is natural, is not it?
会失去自信也是人之常情吧
Stop, stop!
别说了
Don't praise me like that.
你别这么夸我
So, are you worried about the other members?
所以呢 你是在担心其他风纪委员吗
No. Well. Of course, I worry about them.
不是啦 虽然也是会担心没错
I believe there is an issue with my inability to assist them.
我认为无法帮助他们的自己也有问题
I want to help and solve their problems.
我想帮他们解难排忧
So I tried various ways to encourage them.
所以想尽办法鼓励他们
But they always respond like this,
但他们总是会对我说
"That's something only the president can do."
"那是委员长你才做得到的事情"
Oh, so what it sounds like to you
也就是说
is that they are saying, "You can't possibly know how I feel."
在学姐听来 那句话就像是在说 "你不可能理解我的感受"
So you really care about that?
所以你很在意是吗
Y-Yes.
嗯... 没错
You're really straightforward.
你还真是直截了当
To be honest, I'm just like the other members.
真要说起来 我跟其他风纪委员也是同一类人
As a bystander, however, I may be able to see this more objectively.
但我身为一个旁观者 或许能客观地看待这件事
Really?
真的吗
To be frank,
坦白说
they don't really expect your encouragement.
他们根本不期待得到学姐的鼓励
What?
什么
T-Then, what should I do?
那我该怎么做才好
Just say, "Don't worry about it,"
只要说一句"别放在心上"
and gently pat their shoulders.
再轻拍他们的肩膀
That's enough to satisfy them.
大家就心满意足了
The other members definitely don't want you
其他风纪委员
to lower yourself to empathize with them.
一定不希望你拉低自己身份 去跟他们感同身受
They simply hope that
而是希望
you will continue to lead them forward.
你能不断地带领他们向前迈进
That's it?
就这样吗
That's it.
就是这样
To have the respected president pat their shoulders?
敬重的学姐拍自己的肩膀耶
They must be overjoyed.
他们应该开心得都要升天了吧
Am I some kind of goddess?!
我是什么女神吗
Maybe to them,
说不定对他们而言
you're even more revered than a goddess.
学姐你比女神还要崇高吧
Really?
是吗
I see.
原来是这样啊
Sorry for subjecting you to this during your break.
抱歉 休息时间还让你听我倾诉
It's fine. I'm off. See you again if there's a chance.
不会 那我先走了 以后有缘再见
Wait!
等一下
By the way, I don't even know your name.
话说回来 我还不知道你叫什么名字
My last name is Yamazaki.
我姓山崎
Yamazaki.
山崎同学
I still don't think your kindness is unnecessary.
我还是不认为你的善意是多余的
STUDENT COUNCIL How could there be kindness that isn't accepted in this world?
(风纪) 世上怎么会有不被接受的善意呢
Is that so?
是吗...
If you drop it, you'll see.
要是弄掉了我就要你好看
What's with all the women this week?
这礼拜我怎么老是惹到女人
Hey, you.
我说你啊
I made that up, I never thought that way!
我胡乱瞎说的 小的哪敢有这种想法
Did you talk to that girl afterward?
你后来跟那个女生还有在讲话吗
Huh?
什么
Oh, you mean Natsukawa?
哦 你说夏川啊
We were just chatting. After all, we were classmates.
就正常相处咯 我不过就是个同班同学罢了
You won't be popular with girls like that, you know.
你这样是不会受女生欢迎的哦
Huh? You're telling me this now?
啊？这又不是一天两天的事了
You…
你啊
What?
干嘛
Go have a proper conversation with her.
你去跟人家好好谈谈吧
Good morning.
早安
Good morning…
学姐早...
Hey.
我说
What's wrong?
怎么了
No, it's nothing.
没什么啦...
Oh, I see.
哦 是哦
Goodbye, I'm going this way.
再见 我走这边
Ahhhhhh!
啊啊啊啊啊！
I found Sajo!
找到小佐城了
No good, no good! Sajo, you're in big trouble!
不好了 大事不好啦小佐城
The student council president, Rin, is furious!
那个风纪委员长 凛大人气炸了
What?
啊？
Alright, don't worry about me, you go in first!
好吧 芦田你不用管我 你就先进去吧
No way!
才不要
You're pretending to be a gentleman, but you're actually forcing it on others!
你这是假装女士优先 其实根本是强人所难
Then Natsukaga, you go first.
那夏川你先
-What? -Uh, sorry.
-啊？ -呃 对不起
Oh no!
糟了
Morning, I thought you wouldn't come to the morning meeting.
早啊 我还以为你不会来参加朝会了
M-Morning, Senior Shinomiya.
早... 早安 四之宫学姐
Good morning, Junior "Yamazaki".
早啊 “山崎”学弟
So, Sajo, who calls himself Yamazaki.
这位自称山崎的佐城学弟
Yes!
是！
I will be waiting for you in the Student Counseling Center during your lunch break.
午休时间我会在学生指导室等你
Yes.
好
Let's go, Yuyu.
走吧 由结
I've finished my business here.
我要办的事情已经办完了
Yes.
是
Those are from the student council, right?
那是风纪委员会的人对吧
What on earth did you do?
你到底做了什么
Sajo!
佐城！
You dare to impersonate me!
你这家伙竟敢冒充我
Give me back my heartthrob!
害我白白心动了一场
So that's your type, huh?
原来那是你的菜啊
Huh?
啊？
Senior Shinomiya.
四之宫学姐
Uh, well.
呃 这个嘛
If I have to say, I guess so.
真要说的话也算是吧
Great, Yamazaki, she called your name.
太好了山崎 她叫了你的名字
Oh, oh.
啊 是啊
(Dreaming Boy is a Realist, The)
《满怀美梦的少年是现实主义者》
Hey, Sajo!
喂 小佐城
How do you know President Rin?
你怎么会认识凛大人
It's a long story. I accidentally gave her a fake name.
说来话长 我不小心就报了个假名
Idiot! You wasted a rare chance to be favored!
笨蛋 你竟然糟蹋了难得的受宠机会
What are you talking about?
你胡说什么啊
STUDENT COUNSELING CENTER
(学生指导室)
You don't appear to want to apologize?
看来你是不打算道歉吗
Not at all.
不是这样的
I deeply regret not being able to have lunch yesterday.
因为上次没吃到午餐 我事后反省了一番
So this time I bought two.
所以这次我买了两个
Senior, you know what I mean, right?
学姐 你懂我的意思吧
This one is for you, please.
这一个给你
As you can see, Yuyu is here too, huh?
如你所见 由结也在这里耶
Please enjoy this spare Chocolate Triangle Pie.
这是备用的三角巧克力派 请笑纳
Spare.
备用的...
I'm sorry!
对不起
Please.
请收下
-Anyway, sit down first. -Yes.
-总之你先坐下吧 -遵命
Alright, Sajo, why did you lie?
好了 佐城 你为何要说谎
Was it just a prank, or was there a reason?
只是单纯的恶作剧 还是有什么原因
To be honest,
我就直话直说了
I think
因为我总觉得
student council president remembering my name will cause problems.
被风纪委员长记住名字只会惹上麻烦
So I subconsciously said a classmate's name.
所以下意识地说出了同学的名字
I-I see.
这样啊...
I'm quite hurt.
听起来有点伤人耶
But,
但是
aren't you just pushing the trouble onto your classmate?
你这样不是把麻烦事推给同学了吗
Yamazaki was very happy.
山崎他很高兴哦
What? Is that so?
什么 这样啊
No, I don't understand!
不对 我不懂
Why would someone be happy about something that makes someone else unhappy?
为什么有人不情愿 有人却很乐意
Uh, well.
呃 这个嘛
Senior Inatomi appears to have grasped.
看来稻富学姐可以理解这点
Ah, yes.
啊 是...
Uh, that.
呃 那个
Hey, don't do that, you're scaring Yuyu.
喂 你吓到由结了
I'm very sorry.
我很抱歉
I was just kidding.
我开玩笑的啦
Why do you always apologize so easily?
你怎么总是动不动就道歉
No, in the end, I did scare someone.
不 以结果来说我就是吓到人了
Uh, I-I think…
呃 我觉得...
The reason that Yamazaki felt happy
那位山崎同学之所以感到高兴
is because Rin is very beautiful.
是因为凛学姐很漂亮
What? S-Stop joking.
啊？什么啊
Yuyu, don't join him in making jokes.
由结你别跟他一样乱开玩笑
I-I'm serious.
我 我是说真的
Anyway, Sajo,
总而言之 佐城
lying about your name is not good.
谎报姓名不是件好事
I'm very sorry.
对不起
Mm, don't do it next time.
嗯 你以后要注意
Yes.
是
Ah, w-wait!
啊... 等... 等一下
Sajo, wait.
佐城 等等
I didn't call you here for this.
我叫你来并不是为了这个
Huh?
咦？
Yuyu has been feeling guilty
由结她
for rejecting your kindness that day.
那天拒绝了你的好意 她一直很过意不去
So she wants to apologize to you and formally thank you.
所以她想向你道歉 并正式道谢
Thank me? But I didn't help you carry anything.
道谢？可是我没帮学姐你搬东西呀
I… At that time…
我 我当时...
I sabotaged your good intentions.
糟蹋了佐城学弟的…一片好意
I'm sorry.
对不起
Mm.
嗯
Also…
还 还有...
You saw that I was carrying something heavy and offered to help.
你看到我搬着很重的东西 特地过来说要帮忙
Thank you!
谢谢你
No, it's nothing.
这没什么
Um…
那个...
I-I will keep working hard
我 我会继续...
to overcome my fear of men.
努力克服对男性的恐惧
Please go for it.
嗯 学姐加油
I'll take my leave first.
那我先告辞了
See you again if there's a chance.
有缘再见
Sajo, Sajo.
小佐城 小佐城
-So cute. -This one too?
-好可爱 -就是旁边这个吗
Wow, that's a relief.
唉呀 这真令人欣慰
Great, Natsukawa.
太好了 夏川
Why are you giving that fatherly look?
你干嘛一副老父亲的眼神
Ashida, why don't you join them?
芦田你不过去吗？
I am going to join them.
我要啊
What about you?
小佐城你呢？
I will just…
我就…
Forget it.
算了吧
As I thought, am I a stumbling block for Natsukawa?
看来我真的是夏川的绊脚石吧
Huh? What's this?
咦
NEW MESSAGE, KAEDE
(新信息 枫) 这什么
I only have a bad feeling.
我有不祥的预感
How old is she now?
她现在几岁了？
Sorry.
啊 抱歉
What did you say just now?
呃 你刚才说什么
I was asking how old your sister Airi is.
她问你妹妹爱莉现在几岁了
Oh. Well.
啊 嗯
AFTER SCHOOL, STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
(放学后 学生会办公室)
Are you some kind of bossy CEO?
这是什么霸道总裁啊…
…DON'T RUN AWAY, OKAY?
(……不准逃走哦？)
Well…
唉唷！
STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
(学生会办公室)
So, what do you want me for?
所以你找我来干嘛
There is a lot of information to organize
暑假期间的校园参观日
for the summer vacation campus open day.
有很多资料需要整理
Even if we are just filling numbers, more people are better.
我们忙得不可开交 很缺人手
Come and help.
你来帮忙吧
So I am just here for filling numbers.
原来我是你的人手
I'm sure many people would agree
学生会副会长只要开个口
to the request of the student council vice president.
应该有很多人都会答应吧
Anyway, you're good at document organization, right?
反正你很擅长文书处理
I will pretend
你之前
I did not know you lied about your age for a job.
谎报年龄去打工这件事 我都装作不知情了
So work hard.
你就好好工作吧
What? Is Kaede's little brother a delinquent?
原来枫的弟弟是不良少年吗
No, I'm a serious and diligent villager A.
不 我是认真勤奋的村民A
But this is in the city.
但这里是城市耶
You are not a common villager if you are Kaede's younger brother.
身为枫的弟弟那一刻起 就不是普通的村民了吧
Well, that's true.
那倒也是
That's right.
没错
I will leave the data calculation to you.
麻烦你统计一下这些资料
Organize the results into three A4 pages for presentation.
把统计结果整理为 3页A4尺寸的简报就好了
Y-Yes, sir.
是 遵命
Oh, you're doing a good job.
哦 做得不错嘛
Your previous training wasn't in vain.
不枉你之前的一番磨炼啊
I'm very grateful.
多谢抬举
See, I told you, right?
你们看 跟我说的一样吧
Indeed, efficient and accurate.
的确 他手脚俐落又准确
The layout is also very clear.
排版也很清楚明了
No, I'm not that great.
啊 不 没有啦
You are not going to call me over again tomorrow, are you?
你该不会明天也想叫我过来吧
Okay, I'll buy you an adult magazine, alright?
我买点黄色书刊给你行了吧
-The big one.
-大尺寸的
Ahem.
咳咳
Well, it's not out of the question.
嗯 要我帮忙也不是不行啦
How disgusting.
真恶心
Meet at 7:00 sharp tomorrow morning.
明早7点 务必准时集合
Hey, that's a bit…
喂 这有点...
It already feels like summer.
已经有夏天的感觉了
Ah. Y-Yes!
啊 是 是的
Are you thinking about Sajo?
你在想佐城的事吗
After all, he's a junior.
他毕竟是学弟
He's a bit rude, but not rough, right?
虽然有些无礼 但性格并不粗暴 不是吗
Yeah.
是啊
But it seems like
但是我
I said something that made him angry.
好像说了什么惹他生气的话
How could that be?
怎么会
Because Sajo had a dissatisfied look
因为 佐城学弟
in his eyes when he looked at me.
他看着我的眼神似乎有些不满
Dissatisfied?
不满？
Is it because I said I wanted to overcome my fear of men
是因为我说要克服对男性的恐惧
and it made him angry?
所以惹他生气了吗
Don't worry, Yuyu.
放心吧 由结
You didn't do anything wrong.
你没做错什么
Rin.
凛学姐
Hmph.
哼
Hey, Natsukawa.
对了 夏川同学
Can I visit your house next time?
下次能不能去你家玩啊？
-My house? -Your sister is so cute!
-来我家？ -你妹妹真的好可爱
Oh, I haven't seen her for a long time.
我也好久没看到她了
Uh, do you want to come?
呃 那你们要来吗
-Yes! -Thank you.
-好耶 -真开心
Let's go buy a cake!
我们买蛋糕过去吧
Sajo, Sajo.
小佐城 小佐城
We're discussing whether we should go to Aika's house.
我们正在讨论要去小爱家玩呢
Really? But my level isn't high enough.
真的假的 但我等级还不够耶
Natsukawa's house isn't a dungeon.
夏川同学家又不是什么地下城
There are so many people, is it okay?
人这么多 没关系吗
I won't let you get close to Airi.
我才不会让你靠近爱莉
I knew it.
我就知道
Huh?
啊？
128√e980÷2.
128√e980÷2
What about next weekend?
刚才讨论的事 我们约下周末如何呢
Um, it should be no problem.
啊 嗯 应该没问题
Great.
好耶
Definitely a melon bun.
绝对是菠萝面包啦
Alas.
唉…
I really don't want to go…
我真不想去…
Hey.
喂
Huh? What's wrong?
咦？啊 怎么了吗
Well…
呃 那个...
You really won't come?
你真的不来吗
Huh? Where to?
啊？去哪里
-My house… -Hello, Sajo.
-就是来我家… -佐城啊
You haven't left yet?
你还没走啊
I have something to talk to Sajo.
我有事想找佐城
If you guys are discussing something, you can go ahead and finish first.
如果你们还在讨论事情 我就等你们忙完再说
No, it's fine.
不 没关系
You guys go ahead and chat.
你们聊吧
STUDENT COUNSELING CENTER
(学生指导室) 你找我什么事呢
First, I want to thank you.
我要先跟你道谢
Because I followed your advice,
因为听从了你的建议
I successfully helped Yuyu.
我成功帮到了由结
Is that so? That's great.
是吗 那太好了
-But other problems have arisen. -Oh?
-但是又出现了其他问题 -哦？
Well, how should I put it?
就是 该怎么说
Yuyu feels like
由结她啊
she hasn't been understood by you,
觉得没有得到你的理解
so she's very disappointed.
所以感到很失落
How could that be?
怎么会呢
Her goal is to overcome her fear of male students, right?
消除对男学生的恐惧心理 是她的目标对吧
I think it's a great goal.
我认为这个目标很好啊
Yeah.
嗯
Ouch.
好痛
I want to know your true thoughts.
我想知道你的真心话
I'm just disappointed.
我只是感到失望而已
Senior Inatomi's determination isn't enough.
稻富学姐的决心还不够
Go on.
你说吧
The reason Senior Inatomi apologized to me
稻富学姐之所以向我道歉
is not just for me.
并不只是为了我
It's because she despises herself,
而是因为她讨厌那个
her fear of men has ruined the kindness of others.
由于害怕男性 而糟蹋了他人好意的自己
That's what I think.
我是这么认为的
Do you have any objections?
你有什么不满吗
No. On the contrary, I genuinely admire Senior Inatomi.
怎么会呢 不如说我打从心底赞赏稻富学姐
The problem is what happened afterward.
问题在于之后
Senior Inatomi's words
稻富学姐说的话
sounded as if
听起来就好像是
she was using the incident with me
她利用我们之间发生的事
to proclaim that she was working hard to overcome her fear of men.
宣称自己正在努力克服对男性的恐惧
Is that not okay?
这样不行吗
Then she shouldn't have brought you over.
既然如此她就不该带你过来
STUDENT COUNCIL If the president is standing by her side,
（风纪） 如果身边站着风纪委员长
of course she can be fearless and courageous.
那当然能无所畏惧 鼓起勇气吧
That's just what I think.
我只是这么认为罢了
You're really strict.
你还真是严厉
That's not the case.
没这回事
Senior Inatomi as a mascot is the best.
作为吉祥物的稻富学姐是最棒的
I agree.
我同意
But you do pay close attention to people.
不过 你观察人还真是仔细
I used to only focus on one person.
因为我以前一直只注视着一个人
But I won't do that anymore.
只是现在不再那么做了
Can I go now?
那我可以走了吗
Airi, choose the flavor you like.
小爱莉 选个你喜欢的口味吧
Wow! Awesome.
哇 好棒
No, the guest should choose first.
不行 你要让客人先选吧
Okay.
好
So cute!
好可爱
Please enjoy.
请慢用
My name is Nonoka.
我叫乃乃香
Please, Sis Nonoka.
乃乃香姐姐请用
My name is Takaaki.
我叫贵明
Takaki?
贵米…？
-Taka-a-ki. -Taka-Taka, Takaaki.
-贵...明... -贵明
-You got it right. -Yay!
-念对了 -好耶
Let's not waste any time and start eating.
那我们就开动吧